<?xml version='1.0'?>
	<rss version='2.0'>
	<channel>
	<title>Latest events</title>
	<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html</link>
	<description />
	<item>
		<title>XTREME BUGS - 10/17/2014 - 4/12/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;XTREME BUGS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come Experience the Wonder!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Xtreme BUGS are marching, flying, and crawling into Union Station!&amp;nbsp; Get up close to these massive, moving, and buzzing insect and arthropod (invertebrate animal having an external skeleton)&amp;nbsp;models.&amp;nbsp; Come experience an environment that is larger than we are!&amp;nbsp; Get up close and personal with 100 giant bugs that are usually hidden from view.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13569</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Its Honor is Here Pledged and To Honor the Unidentified - Art Exhibit - 2/5/2015 - 5/13/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ITS HONOR IS HERE PLEDGED &amp;amp; TO HONOR THE UNIDENTIFIED - ART EXHIBIT&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Following the critical and popular success of the Nerman Museum's recent exhibition of its estimable contemporary American Indian art collection, the Nerman will present installations by Gina Adams and Natalie Ball within three of the museum's second-floor galleries.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GINA ADAMS:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Lawrence, Kansas-based artist Gina Adams (of Ojibwa ancestry) will exhibit new works utilizing vintage quilts - all overlaid with text drawn from historic treaties between the U.S. government and Native peoples.&amp;nbsp; The quilts will be suspended within the musuem's Cohen Gallery, creating an installation that envelops the viewer.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NATALIE BALL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chiloquin, Oregon-based artist Natalie Ball (whose heritage includes Modoc and Afric...']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13730</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Possible Impossible:  Terry Allen Study Drawings for Public Works - 2/6/2015 - 5/2/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;POSSIBLE IMPOSSIBLE: TERRY ALLEN STUDY DRAWINGS FOR PUBLIC WORKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Terry Allen is back with a new exhibition of drawings, sketches and photographs related to his public art commissions. The exhibition opens on First Friday, February 6 and continues through Saturday, May 2, 2015.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVENT TIMES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday to Friday:&amp;nbsp; 10am to 4pm&lt;br /&gt;Saturday:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Noon to 4pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Above Picture by Terry Allen:&amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Modern Communication&lt;/em&gt; (detail), 1993 for Police &amp;amp; Fire Dept., Communication Center, 27&quot; x 21&quot;&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13717</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Fairy Tale Village Exhibit - 2/7/2015 - 5/3/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FAIRY TALE VILLAGE EXHIBIT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Children's tales come to life as you walk into a world of make-believe to interact with characters from favorite stories and rhymes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visit the Snow Queen in her Ice Palace. Experience the giant adventures of &quot;Jack and the Beanstalk.&quot; Sit in Cinderella's magic carriage or stroll with &quot;Little Red Riding Hood&quot; through the woods to Grandmother's house. This interactive exhibit includes a reading area where parents can share their favorite stories with their kids. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Register to win a Fairy Tale Village prize package, which includes a private party at the exhibit, gift bag of toys from Crown Center merchants and a $100 Crown Center gift certificate!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVENT TIMES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday-Saturday - 10am to 6pm&lt;br /&gt;Sunday - Noon to 6pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADDITIONAL INFORMA...']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13787</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Broadway and Back - 2/27/2015 - 3/29/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BROADWAY AND BACK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lush scores, lavish costumes, lively plots and loving characters.&amp;nbsp; These ingredients make great stage musicals.&amp;nbsp; They also make great movies.&amp;nbsp; No wonder so many musicals have been translated from stage to screen.&amp;nbsp; Featuring songs from the classic musicals of Rodgers and Hammerstein, Irving Berlin, Jule Styne, and Cole Porter, plus contemporary hits such as &lt;em&gt;The Producers&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Thoroughly Modern Millie&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Sunset Boulevard&lt;/em&gt; and&lt;em&gt; Disney&lt;/em&gt; favorites.&amp;nbsp; You'll love this tribute to works that made the leap from Broadway to Hollywood and vice versa.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13768</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Carmen, or Don't Cry for Me Martin City! - 2/28/2015 - 5/3/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CARMEN, OR DON'T CRY FOR ME MARTIN CITY!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a sharp, clever twist to the acting days when men played women, Martin City's title role will be played by a MAN!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't miss&amp;nbsp;the ridiculousness of Carmen's adventure where maracas, bull fighters and characters alike are mixed up for the sake of mayhem and refreshing family fun!&amp;nbsp; Following the melodrama will be the Vaudeville, Topsy Turvy Tunes!, a celebration of Martin City's cheeringly funny vaudeville numbers over the past 30 years!&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADMISSION:&amp;nbsp; (Reservations Essential)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket Prices:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Matinees - $10.99&lt;br /&gt;Evenings - $12.99&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13763</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Nick Joerling:  Dreaming in Form - 3/6/2015 - 4/18/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NICK JOERLING: DREAMING IN FORM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sensuality and humor are qualities inherent in Nick Joerling's expressive and gestural forms. His non-traditional techniques challenge the constraints of utility, resulting in pots that entertain risky possibilities. This exhibition opens First Friday, March 6 and continues through Saturday, April 18.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVENT TIMES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wednesday - Frida: 10am to 5pm&lt;br /&gt;Saturday: Noon to 4pm&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13723</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Bingo Every Monday Night - 3/9/2015 - 1/4/2016</title>
		<description><![CDATA['The Best BINGO Place in Overland Park.....Is Now BETTER!

ABDALLAH SHRINERS at 5300 Metcalf Ave, Near I-35 and I-635 Announce......
Smoke Free BINGO Every Monday Night

2 Progressive Games - (Jackpots Up to $1,000 ea) 
$500 Jackpot Game Each Week - Pull Tabs
Free Soft Drinks &amp; Reasonable Concessions
Safe Parking
Doors Open 6 PM - Bingo At 7 PM
Come Enjoy Our New Clean FRESH Air At Abdallah Shriners
Johnson County's Best Bingo
show contact info 
All Bingo Proceeds Benefit The Abdallah Shriners. Player Costs Are Not Deductible As A Charity Contribution']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13767</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Antarctica Above and Below the Ice - 3/16/2015 - 3/16/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANTARCTICA ABOVE AND BELOW THE ICE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Join Marine Biologist Lin Craft as she explores the great white continent, Antarctica, through pictures on Monday, March 16th at 5:00 p.m.&amp;nbsp; See this continent like never before, from the unique vantage point of a working scientist.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through these amazing photos you will dive through six feet of ice to explore the fascinating life of the ocean floor.&amp;nbsp; Enjoy the unique wildlife of the world above water featuring seals, penguins and killer whales.&amp;nbsp; Discover the pristine beauty of this icy realm while exploring spectacular ice caves inside floating glaciers.&amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADMISSION:&amp;nbsp; (RSVP - This event is included in the Zoo Admission)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Adult (Ages 11+) - $13.50&lt;br /&gt;Senior (55+) - $12.50&lt;br /&gt;Child (Ages 3-11) - $10.50&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13789</link>
	</item>
  	<item>
		<title>Sue Gingrich Fine Art Showing - 3/16/2015 - 4/16/2015</title>
		<description><![CDATA['&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SUE GINGRICH FINE ART SHOWING&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Sue Gingrich artwork has arrived at Prairiebrooke.&amp;nbsp; Her work will be featured in the Prairiebrooke Gallery along with works of Wilfred, Eventov, Boucher, Klimova, Haynes and Ichter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GALLERY HOURS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Monday-Friday - 10:00am to 5:30pm&lt;br /&gt;Saturday - 10:00am to 5:00pm&lt;br /&gt;Third Friday Local Life - Extended hours from 10:00am to 8:00pm&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;']]></description>
		<link>http://www.visitoverlandpark.com/events.html?id=13806</link>
	</item>
  </channel>
</rss>