<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:taxo="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/taxonomy/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Events</title>
    <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com//visitors-and-residents/calendar-of-events/</link>
    <description>Events</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 16:54:08 GMT</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>17th Annual Lebanese Festival</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/17th-Annual-Lebanese-Festival/31199/</link>
      <description>04-04-2015 to 04-04-2015 - The best Lebanese food you will ever eat!&#xD;
Authentic falafel, Hummus, Tabouli, Shawarma, Baklava and sweets.&#xD;
Belly dancers, folkloric dance, talent competition, Miss Tabouli 2015 contest, Fortune teller, Easter bunny and more!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 03:54:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer &amp; Bacon Fest</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/Beer-Bacon-Fest/30545/</link>
      <description>03-28-2015 to 03-28-2015 - 75 Craft Beers, 10 Restaurants, 10 Bacons From Across the U.S... and lots of Piggy Love!&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Last Year's Festival was a huge hit but it was just the beginning! Cary's Porkiest Playtime returns and this time it will be even better. The all-you-care-to-taste extravaganza comes complete with the best craft beers for your tasting pleasure... and of course the food of the Gods: BACON.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Guests enjoy a souvenir glass plus 75+ of their favorite international beers and wines. The first 100 guests in line for each session receive a free &amp;quot;Collectible Bacon&amp;quot; T-Shirt to celebrate the show. VIP Beer and Bacon Admission will host over 10 restaurant tasting stations featuring the best restaurants in the Triangle. They will be on-hand vying for the $500 Best Bacon Dish Prize. (VIP Beer &amp;amp; Bacon Session food tastings included, regular beer tasting session food is ala carte.) Two-tons of gourmet bacons will be griddled on-site (until 3pm). The Main Stage will host live music all day. A Butchering 101 Class will be hosted on the Main Stage! All of this plus fun foodie exhibits and so much more!&amp;nbsp;&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
VIP Session: Advance $69, noon-6pm; Regular Session: Advance $39; On-site $45 (if available), 2-6pm. Designated Driver tickets also available. Visit website for more details.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 10:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking with Chef Arthur</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/Cooking-with-Chef-Arthur/31591/</link>
      <description>03-17-2015 to 03-17-2015 - Cooking Lesson, Four-Course Dinner and Wine Tasting. Experience the Irregardless philosophy and learn cooking techniques to create nourishing foods. It's an evening of fun, laughter and meaningful conversations. Space is limited. Call to reserve your space in this class.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 11:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhibition: Starring North Carolina!</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/Exhibition-Starring-North-Carolina-/27068/</link>
      <description>11-15-2014 to 09-06-2015 - &lt;p&gt;&#xD;
See the first major exhibition about N.C.'s movies, television shows, cast members and crews. &lt;i&gt;Starring North Carolina!&lt;/i&gt; will feature costumes and props from &lt;i&gt;Bull Durham&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Iron Man 3&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Blue Velvet&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;Sleepy Hollow&lt;/i&gt; and dozens more! The approximately 8,000-square-foot exhibit includes interactive components, movie clips and images.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
Some 3,000 films and television programs have been made in the Tar Heel State. Learn about N.C.'s role in the film industry for more than 100 years. The exhibit is sponsored in part by the N.C. Museum of History Associates.&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 06:39:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern Oyster Roast with Live Jazz Music</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/Southern-Oyster-Roast-with-Live-Jazz-Music/31621/</link>
      <description>03-21-2015 to 03-21-2015 - Meet the neighbors at Faire's southern-style oyster roast and enjoy live jazz music by the Doug Largent Trio. Lonerider Brewing Company is sponsoring the evening and creating a special brew for the event. We will be providing a shuck station, wine provided by Undurraga Winery, and craft brews. Dine on the patio of Faire and mix and mingle with those who live in the surrounding area. The menu for the night features authentic southern-style oysters prepared a variety of ways along with other southern favorites.&amp;nbsp;Tickets will go fast so be sure you get yours today.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 12:07:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World's Largest Dinosaurs</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/The-World-s-Largest-Dinosaurs/28279/</link>
      <description>10-11-2014 to 04-12-2015 - &lt;i&gt;The World's Largest Dinosaurs&lt;/i&gt;, a major new exhibition now open at the North Carolina Museum of Natural Sciences, explores the amazing biology of a group of uniquely super-sized dinosaurs: the long-necked and long-tailed sauropods, some of which may have reached lengths of 140 feet. The exhibition draws on cutting-edge paleo-biological research that looks in part to living organisms to make inferences about how these giants were able to thrive, as a group, for more than 100 million years. Through innovative displays - including the exhibition centerpiece, a life-sized, detailed model of a 60-foot-long Mamenchisaurus -&lt;i&gt;The World's Largest Dinosaurs&lt;/i&gt; takes visitors beyond the bones and into the bodies of these titans, shedding light on how heart rate, respiration, metabolism and reproduction are linked to size.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 06:18:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Beer Festival Raleigh</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/World-Beer-Festival-Raleigh/30703/</link>
      <description>04-11-2015 to 04-11-2015 - &lt;div&gt;&#xD;
Find, taste and discover the beer of your dreams! A chance to sample from over 250 craft and specialty beers from around the world.&#xD;
&lt;/div&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
General Admission: $50&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Tasting glass with unlimited 4oz tastings from over 250 of the finest beers!&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Access into the Art of Beer Experience for beer ingredient samplings, pairings, educational seminars, a mini commercial brewery and more!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;&#xD;
VIP Admission: $100&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Tasting glass with unlimited 4oz tastings from over 250 of the finest beers!&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Access into the Art of Beer Experience for beer ingredient samplings, pairings, educational seminars, a mini commercial brewery and more!&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Enjoy a private lounge complete with private bathrooms, food and live music!&lt;br /&gt;&#xD;
&amp;bull;	Three issue subscription to &lt;i&gt;All About Beer Magazine&lt;/i&gt;!&#xD;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 13:18:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"American Classics"</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-American-Classics-/29989/</link>
      <description>03-27-2015 to 03-27-2015 - The program features William Schumans programmatic settings of Walt Whitman poetry, Randall Thompsons settings of Robert Frost poetry, Charles Ives intricate setting of &lt;i&gt;Psalm 90&lt;/i&gt; and Aaron Coplands a cappella rendering of the Creation story, &lt;i&gt;In the Beginning&lt;/i&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 05:58:32 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"HIPsters Delight!"</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-HIPsters-Delight-/30983/</link>
      <description>03-24-2015 to 03-24-2015 - Works by J.S. Bach, Georg Telemann and others featuring&amp;nbsp;Baroque music on period instruments.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 19:46:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Legends, Fairy Tales and Fantasies"</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-Legends-Fairy-Tales-and-Fantasies-/29982/</link>
      <description>03-29-2015 to 03-29-2015 - DVOK   Legends; GUBAIDULINA   Concordanza; RAVEL   Mother Goods; ASKIM   New Work.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 08:15:31 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Rising Stars"</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-Rising-Stars-/30477/</link>
      <description>03-22-2015 to 03-22-2015 - Showcasing winners of RSO's annual statewide concerto competition. Come see tomorrow's stars today! Other selections will include Brahm's Variations on a theme by Haydn.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 22:20:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"The Rutter Requiem"</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-The-Rutter-Requiem-/31874/</link>
      <description>03-15-2015 to 03-15-2015 - The choirs of Church of the Nativity and St. Paul's Cary perform The Rutter Requiem. The musical setting is an adaptation by English Composer John Rutter of the Roam Catholic Requiem Mass and was completed in 1985. The setting features combined choirs, soloist, and orchestral accompaniment. Soloist are Waltye Rasulala and Lynn Hudson. Conducted by Rusty McKinney. No cost for admission. Donations appreciated.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 09:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“SILENCE” Film Project Launch Event</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/-SILENCE-Film-Project-Launch-Event/32111/</link>
      <description>03-15-2015 to 03-15-2015 - Foster A Voice is launching a crowd funding, Kickstarter campaign to raise capital in order to produce the film, &amp;ldquo;SILENCE.&amp;rdquo; The purpose of &amp;ldquo;SILENCE&amp;rdquo; is to make the public aware of the foster care crises that are taking place all around them, to educate those who can help prevent it, and support the programs already in place, such as the Foster Care Foundation, Foster Alumni Association and Kinship Care Programs. &#xD;
The plot chronicles the plight of two sisters who become embroiled in the foster care system. Like so many children in real life, they are separated, moving from home to home and school to school. It depicts the difficulty these children face in finding lasting friendships, becoming involved in school sports or other activities, and keeping up grades due to ever changing curriculums. &#xD;
And just like these girls, what sustains thousands of foster care children, is the hope that someone will open their hearts and consequently their homes to give a foster child a chance to live a normal and healthy life. Otherwise, for far too many children and young people, the cycle never ends. &#xD;
With your help, Foster A Voice will not only continue its mission to be an advocacy group, dedicated to providing a voice to diminish the time and bureaucracy in the foster care system, which hinders so many wonderful people from becoming foster parents. Moreover, it will provide mentorships to help break the cycle of becoming homeless, getting pregnant, not finishing school, going from foster Care to Welfare and their children following their same path.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 13:25:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015 Butterfly Cary Cup Championship Table Tennis Tournament</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/2015-Butterfly-Cary-Cup-Championship-Table-Tennis-Tournament/31370/</link>
      <description>03-19-2015 to 03-22-2015 - This USATT four-star sanctioned table tennis tournament includes a giant round robin event, ratings-based events for single players and doubles teams and offers over $21,500 in prizes. The Butterfly Cary Cup attracts top players from across the country every March, and this year it is hosted for the first time at Triangle Table Tennis, a specialized, world-class venue with over 32 competition tables.  Pre-registration is required.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015 Sangria ThrowDown To Benefit MS</title>
      <link>http://www.visitraleigh.com/includes/calendar-of-events/2015-Sangria-ThrowDown-To-Benefit-MS/32094/</link>
      <description>04-11-2015 to 04-11-2015 - The 2015 Sangria ThrowDown to benefit the fight against multiple sclerosis features sangria tastings, beer tastings, Mike Tefft Re/Max Pig Pickin,' food tastings by Tijuana Flats of Cary, live music by Plan B, salsa dancing and drawings for great prizes. There is a $15 admission fee. All proceeds benefit the National MS Society and Walk MS team #twofeet2acure.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 04:41:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>